{"game_code":"WU7XBFKR","level_name":"Periodical Test","questions":[{"answer":"Data","incorrect":["Information","Files","Knowledge"],"question":"This is the basic building block of information, and it becomes meaningful when processed or interpreted."},{"answer":"It is raw and unprocessed","incorrect":["It is easily understood","It has meaning and context","It is processed and organized"],"question":"What is the primary characteristic of data?"},{"answer":"Information is derived from processing and organizing data","incorrect":["Information is always in a raw and unprocessed state","It has meaning and context","It is processed and organized"],"question":"Which of the following statements is true about information?"},{"answer":"Data communications","incorrect":["Data encryption","Computer programming","Graphical user interface"],"question":"The exchange of information in binary form between two connected devices, whether directly or through a network?"},{"answer":"Interfacing","incorrect":["Synchronization","Signal Generation","Recovery"],"question":"It is one of the communication tasks which refers to the need to convert the input data (digital) into a suitable form (analog) for transmission and vice-versa during reception."},{"answer":"Recovery","incorrect":["Signal Generation","Addressing and routing","Transmission system utilization"],"question":"It allows the system to resume an activity previously interrupted by an unexpected fault in the system. What communication task is that?"},{"answer":"Exchange management","incorrect":["Synchronization","Addressing and routing","Interfacing"],"question":"It is the agreement between devices on various conventions, such as transmission method (simplex, half or full duplex), data block length, data format, error detection and correction, and how fast data must be sent. What communication task is that?"},{"answer":"Synchronization","incorrect":["Signal Generation","Transmission system utilization","Interfacing"],"question":"It is one of the communication tasks wherein it allows the receiver to determine when a signal begins, and when it ends, and how long each signal element is."},{"answer":"System management","incorrect":["Protection","Signal Generation","Exchange management"],"question":"It is one of the communication tasks wherein it is required for configuring and monitoring the system, allowing it to react rationally to failures and overloads, and to effectively plan for future expansion."},{"answer":"Transmission system utilization ","incorrect":["Interfacing","System management","Synchronization"],"question":"It is the need to efficiently use various transmission facilities that are commonly shared by other devices? What communication task is that?"},{"answer":"Addressing and routing","incorrect":["Transmission system utilization","System management","Protection"],"question":"It ensures that in multi-user environment, the information is sent to the correct destination, and that the best possible route to this destination is chosen. What communication task is that?"},{"answer":"Fiber Optic Cable","incorrect":["Shielded Twisted Pair (STP) Cable","Coaxial Cable","Unshielded Twisted Pair (UTP) Cable"],"question":"They are known for their high-speed data transmission capabilities and are commonly used in long-distance and high-bandwidth applications, such as telecommunications networks, data centers, and internet backbones."},{"answer":"Application layer","incorrect":["Session layer","Presentation layer","Physical layer"],"question":"This is the top layer of the OSI model which provides a set of interfaces for sending and receiving applications to gain access to and use network services."},{"answer":"Presentation layer","incorrect":["Transport layer","Session layer","Data Link layer"],"question":"Manages data-format information for networked communications (the networkâ€™s translator)."},{"answer":"Session layer","incorrect":["Network layer","Physical layer","Application layer"],"question":"This layer enables two networked resources to hold ongoing communications (called a session) across a network."},{"answer":"Transport layer","incorrect":["Network layer","Session layer","Presentation layer"],"question":"Manages the transmission of data across a network."},{"answer":"Network layer","incorrect":["Application layer","Data Link layer","Presentation layer"],"question":"Handles addressing messages for delivery, as well as translating logical network addresses and names into their physical counterparts."},{"answer":"Network Interface Cards","incorrect":["Credit Cards","Pokemon Cards","Gift Cards"],"question":"An adapter card that plugs into the system bus of a computer and allows the computer to send and receive signals on a network."},{"answer":"Data Link layer","incorrect":["Application layer","Network layer","Physical layer"],"question":"Handles special data frames (packets) between the Network layer and the Physical layer."},{"answer":"Coaxial Cable","incorrect":["Shielded Twisted Pair (STP) Cable","Fiber Optic Cable","Unshielded Twisted Pair (UTP) Cable"],"question":"It is known for their ability to carry high-frequency signals over long distances with minimal interference. They are widely used for connecting cable television, satellite dishes, and in some cases, broadband modems to homes and businesses."},{"answer":"Unshielded Twisted Pair (UTP) Cable","incorrect":["Shielded Twisted Pair (STP) Cable","Coaxial Cable","Fiber Optic Cable"],"question":"These are prevalent in Ethernet networking, connecting devices like computers, switches, and routers. They are cost-effective and suitable for short to medium-distance network connections."},{"answer":"Shielded Twisted Pair (STP) Cable","incorrect":["Unshielded Twisted Pair (UTP) Cable","Coaxial Cable","Fiber Optic Cable"],"question":"These cables are often used in industrial and commercial settings where there may be higher levels of electromagnetic interference."},{"answer":"Border Gateway Protocol (BGP)","incorrect":["Exterior Gateway Protocol (EGP)","Interior Gateway Routing Protocol (IGRP)","Enhanced Interior Gateway Routing Protocol (EIGRP)"],"question":"It helps manage how packets are routed on the internet via exchange of information between edge routers."},{"answer":"Interior Gateway Routing Protocol (IGRP)","incorrect":["Routing Information Protocol (RIP)","Open Shortest Path First (OSPF)","Enhanced Interior Gateway Routing Protocol (EIGRP)"],"question":"It specifies how routing information will be exchanged between gateways within an independent network."},{"answer":"Routing Information Protocol (RIP)","incorrect":["Exterior Gateway Protocol (EGP)","Open Shortest Path First (OSPF)","Enhanced Interior Gateway Routing Protocol (EIGRP)"],"question":"It determines how routers can share information while transferring traffic among connected group of local area networks."},{"answer":"Enhanced Interior Gateway Routing Protocol (EIGRP)","incorrect":["Border Gateway Protocol (BGP)","Open Shortest Path First (OSPF)","Routing Information Protocol (RIP)"],"question":"In this protocol, if a router is unable to find a path to a destination from the tables, it asks route to its neighbors, and they pass the query to their neighbors until a router has found the path."},{"answer":"Exterior Gateway Protocol (EGP)","incorrect":["Enhanced Interior Gateway Routing Protocol (EIGRP)","Open Shortest Path First (OSPF)","Routing Information Protocol (RIP)"],"question":"It decides how routing information can be exchanged between two neighbor gateway hosts, each of which has its own router."},{"answer":"Router","incorrect":["Switch","Cable","System Unit"],"question":"The physical or virtual internetworking device that is designed to receive, analyze, and forward data packets between computer networks."},{"answer":"Third layer","incorrect":["First layer","Fifth layer","Second layer"],"question":"A router works on the what layer of the OSI model"},{"answer":"A router analyzes a destination IP address of a given packet header and compares it with the routing table to decide the packet's next path, but routers do not use routing tables for this purpose.","incorrect":["Routers are network devices that operate at the Network Layer (Layer 3) of the OSI model.","Routers are used to connect different network segments and route data packets between them.","Routers can perform Network Address Translation (NAT) to allow multiple devices on a local network to share a single public IP address for internet access."],"question":"Which of the following is not true about routers?"},{"answer":"Wireless router","incorrect":["Edge router","Brouter","Core router"],"question":"These routers are used to offer Wi-Fi connectivity to laptops, smartphones, and other devices with Wi-Fi network capabilities, and it can also provide standard ethernet routing for a small number of wired network systems."},{"answer":"Brouter","incorrect":["Edge router","Wireless router","Broadband router"],"question":"A combination of the bridge and a router. It allows transferring the data between networks like a bridge."},{"answer":"Edge router","incorrect":["Core router","Brouter","Broadband router"],"question":"This router is a lower-capacity device that is placed at the boundary of a network."},{"answer":"Core router","incorrect":["Edge router","Brouter","Broadband router"],"question":"A type of router that can route the data within a network, but it is not able to route the data between the networks."},{"answer":"Subscribe edge router","incorrect":["Label edge router","Wireless router","Broadband router"],"question":"This belongs to an end-user organization, and it works in a situation where it acts on a border device."},{"answer":"Label edge router","incorrect":["Subscribe edge router","Wireless router","Broadband router"],"question":"This is used in the boundary of Multiprotocol Label Switching (MPLS) networks. It acts as a gateway between the LAN, WAN, or the internet."},{"answer":"Open Shortest Path First (OSPF)","incorrect":["Border Gateway Protocol (BGP)","Interior Gateway Routing Protocol (IGRP)","Enhanced Interior Gateway Routing Protocol (EIGRP)"],"question":"A routing protocol which is used to calculate the best route for the given packets to reach the destination, as they move via a set of connected networks."}],"time":120}